Hey neighbors! Have you seen this viral dancing realtor going all out for her unsold gem?
Look at that hustle! I'll be honest, I love this energy. What people don't see behind the fun
dances and persistence is the real grind of real estate. That home in Owensboro hasn't sold yet,
but she's not quitting. And neither do I here in Coeur d'Alene and Liberty Lake.
My experience tells me homes linger sometimes due to pricing hiccups,
market shifts, or just needing that fresh marketing spark.
Locally, our lake views and mountain vibes make properties hot, but I've turned stalled listings
around with virtual tours, targeted open houses, and creative staging that highlights those Idaho
sunsets. Persistence pays. Treat yourself to a bold strategy and watch it move.
DM me to chat about your home journey.